Guide to the Pavel Nikolaevich Miliukov Papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Arranged Materials
  - Subseries II.3: Subject Files
    - Financial Reports on Posledniia Novosti (Box 15)
    - Interparliamentary Union (Box 15)
    - Kadets and Duma (Box 15)
    - Kadets in Third Duma (Box 15)
    - Kadets in Civil War (Box 16)
    - Kadets in Emigration, 1919-1920 (Box 16)
    - 1905 (Box 16)
    - Respublikansko-Demokraticheskoe Ob'edinenie (Box 16)
  - Subseries II.4: Estate Files
    - (Box 17)
    - (Box 18)
  - Subseries II.5: Printed Materials and Miscellaneous
    - Ost-Express, 1928 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous printed materials (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous printed materials (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous papers; Business cards (Box 19)